

PROFILE

I am very interested in Cyber Security witch I practice many exploits of websites .

I have good experience with eCommerce more than 3 years of Shopify and Facebook / Instagram Ads, Bing ads, Google AdWords, I sell products Golf and Tennis to my customers in USA,UK and Europe, AU. In addition.

Determined and rigorous, I am looking for a new challenge in Marketing or development, programming. I like team projects that evolve in a dynamic environment.

CONTACT

PHONE:

212-601-233605

WEBSITE:

www.golf-euro.com

EMAIL:

contact@golf-euro.com

LINKEDIN:

/in/marouane-boulhilt/

HOBBIES

Reading computer programming books.
Coding.
Swimming.
Trip.

MAROUANE BOULHILT

INTERNSHIP

EDUCATION

YouCode, Youssoufia.

2018-2019

Software Developer based on the repository developed by Simplon.

Soft Art School of Management and Computer Science, Ben Guerir.

Year technician specialized in Development Computer.

Al khawarizmy, Casablanca.

2013 - 2016

Superior Technician Certificate in materials Plastics and Composites, Molding.

Jaber Ibn Hayane, Youssoufia.

2012 - 2013

I get my Bachelor of Science and Mechanical Technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

E-pocket Project

Jun-2019

programming the application with ionic framework using angular 4 and TypeScript. In addition I control the part of visual identity of the project.

Shopify Store, eCommerce

November 2015-December 2018

selling products to many countries. Like USA, UK, EU, AU.

OCP Group intern

March 2016-April 2016

quality control of phosphate collected by farmers at different stages of production in order to quantitatively estimate the value of treatments and meet an increasingly demanding clientele.

SKILLS

